<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dynamics NAV on E-Ship Guy</title><link>https://eshipguy.com/categories/dynamics-nav/</link><description>Recent content in Dynamics NAV on E-Ship Guy</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 02:04:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://eshipguy.com/categories/dynamics-nav/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>On-Line Help for E-Ship</title><link>https://eshipguy.com/on-line-help-for-e-ship/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 02:04:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eshipguy.com/on-line-help-for-e-ship/</guid><description>&lt;p>When you implement the E-Ship/EDI functionality in your database, you get a lot of new fields added also. A lot of those fields are added in places users already interact and as such questions often come up, as to the functionality of certain fields.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The good thing is, that Lanham &amp;amp; Associates over the years have developed some help text, which is a good start – and it is getting better and better.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>NAV EasySecurity</title><link>https://eshipguy.com/nav-easysecurity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 20:09:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eshipguy.com/nav-easysecurity/</guid><description>&lt;p>I just want to let you know, that I am still breathing! I have for the past couple of weeks been doing an implementation of &lt;a href="http://mergetool.com/products/easysecurity.html">EasySecurity&lt;/a>, that has taken up all my time.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This customer is a public company and as such needs to adhere to SOX regulations.&lt;/p>
&lt;p> &lt;/p>
&lt;p>One thing I have learned about SOX; The US Government must be jealous – so much bureaucracy to do anything!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Blind or Double Blind Shipments</title><link>https://eshipguy.com/blindshipments/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 22:58:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eshipguy.com/blindshipments/</guid><description>&lt;p>In this world of easy e-commerce solutions we often find us in a situation companies manage orders for other companies, and want to ensure that end customers not know about it. This can be accommodated in Standard eShip using Blind or Double Blind Shipment.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>When using &lt;strong>Blind Shipment&lt;/strong>, the Return Address on the Package (and label) will be populated with the information from the &lt;strong>Bill-To Customer&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Welcome to the E-Ship Guy's Blog</title><link>https://eshipguy.com/welcome/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2010 21:12:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eshipguy.com/welcome/</guid><description>Having worked with E-Ship since 2001 I, at times, feel that a lot of people thinks that E-Ship is just for printing UPS and FedEx labels. E-Ship is so much more.
My goal with this blog is to hopefully provide help and inspiration to other consultants and end-customer alike and show some of the tips and tricks I have used over the years.
Please let me know if you have any specific areas you are curious about by commenting on this post!</description></item></channel></rss>